KEVIN (CHANH P.), NGO

N Lincoln Ave, Monterey Park, CA - 91755 · (+1) 626 877 3058 pngo19@calstatela.edu · https://www.linkedin.com/in/fkvn/ · https://github.com/fkvn

By picturing myself as a Full-Stack developer and concerning my long-term goals, I want to be an expert on the website development field, especially of progressive Web Applications, which predictably become the major competitor to mobile apps in the modern age. In addition, wherever I go, people are always willing to write a recommendation letter for me and give me a positive performance review. I'm proud to say that my secure communication, outstanding attitude, and impressive leadership skills set me apart from other programmers.

EDUCATION

08/2018 - PRESENT

M.S., COMPUTER SCIENCE, CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LOS ANGELES

GPA: 4.0

1/2017 - 5/2018

ENGLISH STUDIES, CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LONG BEACH (ALI)

GPA: 4.0

8/2011 - 4/2016

B.S., COMPUTER SCIENCE, HO CHI MINH CITY, UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

GPA: 3.1

SKILLS

BACK-END: Java/Java EE, Maven/Spring Boot, Hibernate/JPA, C#/.NET Core, Node.js/Express, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and Python.

TOOLS AND SOFTWARE: Git/GitHub, Microsoft Office, Eclipse, VS Code, Visual Studio, and others.

FRONT-END: HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Bootstrap, and React.

OTHERS: Machine Learning, Leadership, and Problem/solving,

PROJECTS

HIRING PROCESS SERVICE

This project is developed based on a school project of "Advanced Topics in Web Programming" class for master students at California State University, Los Angeles - 2019. The primary purpose is for approaching how to implement Rest API backend with Spring Boot application.

Technology: Java/Maven/Spring, Spring Boot, MySQL, REST API.

Details: https://github.com/fkvn/Hiring-Process-Service

POS SYSTEM SERVICE

The goal of the project is to develop a server-side API service to facilitate the management process for a small-medium coffee shop. Owners can track hours, communicate with employees, and perform other tasks that help their store run smoothly.

Technology: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, REST API. **Details**: https://github.com/fkvn/POS-System-Service

CUSTOMERS-ORDERS SERVICE

Mainly developing a server-side API service to facilitate the management process for real medium businesses. This project is developed based on requests from a Cal State LA student for his family business.

Technology: C#, ASP.NET Core, PostgreSQL, REST API. **Details**: https://github.com/fkvn/Customers-Orders-Service

EXPERIENCE

10/2018 - PRESENT

ASSISTANT LAB CONSULTANT, CAL STATE LA – ITS (IT CLIENT SUPPORT SERVICES)

Attend customer service and keep updated on ITS services available for campus users. One of the most challenging things is maintaining lab services for software, security, and helping students most appropriately. In addition to my tech-savvy skills, I devote particular emphasis to punctuality, handling under pressure, and maintaining outstanding performance.

7/2014 - 10/2014

DEVELOPER INTERN, ISB VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED (IVC)

Communicated with the supervisor to implement multiple tasks related, mainly, to Visual Basic for Application (VBA) for Microsoft Excel. Primarily working on analyzing, researching, and implementing data from excel files to export expected results in terms of business/client demand.

ACTIVITIES

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LOS ANGELES

Cal State LA MESA Prelims 2019.

Regional Middle School Science Bowl (RSB) from the U.S.

130th annual Rose Parade celebration – Rose Parade Float Decorating.

ECST Open House in Partnership with Boeing Training Dates.

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LONG BEACH.

Student Ambassador.

CSULB Phi Delta Conference.

LANGUAGES

VIETNAMESE ENGLISH CHINESE

Native or Bilingual Full Professional Limited Working